curiosity.com 2018-10-02

# Privacy Policy

Last Modified: May 22, 2018

Beacon Solutions, Inc., d/b/a Curiosity.com ("Curiosity", “we” or “us”) understands that security and privacy are important issues for visitors to and users of [curiosity.com](https://curiosity.com/), associated subdomains, such as [about.curiosity.com](https://about.curiosity.com/), or [curiosity.app](https://curiosity.app/), our Curiosity mobile applications, and other digital and interactive services that link to this privacy policy (collectively, the "Services"). The following Privacy Policy (the "Policy") sets forth Curiosity's privacy practices regarding its collection, use and sharing of the information that Curiosity gathers via the Services and about users of the Services.

Before you submit any information on or through the Services, please carefully review this Policy along with our [Terms of Use](https://curiosity.com/terms) and any other documents refer to within this Policy to understand how we will collect and utilize your information and your choices about this information. By using any part of the Services, you consent to our use of such information as described in this Policy. Your use of our Services, and any dispute over privacy, is subject to this Policy and our [Terms of Use](https://curiosity.com/terms), including its applicable limitations on damages and the resolution of disputes. Our [Terms of Use](https://curiosity.com/terms) are incorporated by reference into this Policy. We will continue to assess this Policy as we change our offerings or as new regulation come into place, and we may make changes to this Policy.  Any changes will be posted here and you should check this page on occasion for updates.  Your continued use of the Services will signify acceptance of the terms of an updated Policy.  

This Policy only applies to information collected through the Services and not to information collected offline or to information you may provide to third-party sites to which Curiosity may link, except as expressly provided herein.  

For the purpose of data protection laws applicable to you, based on your location and the point in time for which you provide your information (“Applicable Law”), Curiosity will be the ‘data controller’ or the equivalent under your Applicable Law. 

### Table of Contents

Collection of Information

Use of Information

Information Sharing

Personalized Content and Advertising

Privacy of Children

Your Choices

Your California Privacy Rights

External Links

International Transfer

Security

Privacy Policy Modifications

Contacting Curiosity

### Collection of Information

We may collect information directly from you, automatically through your use of our Services, and from third-party sources. We may combine all of the information we collect about you.

#### Information Collected Directly From You

We may collect information from you during your use of the Services when you:

  * Register for an account; 

  * Fill in forms; 

  * Search for articles or subjects; 

  * Purchase an Ad free subscription; 

  * Enter a sweepstakes or contest or register for a contest; 

  * Complete a survey or provide us with feedback; 

  * Subscribe to email or push notifications;  

  * Communicate with us; 

  * Report a problem with our website; or  

  * Post user generated content to or on any of our Services. 

The information you provide to us may include but is not limited to your (i) name; (ii) email address; (iii) address; (iv) phone numbers or other contact information; (v) age and/or date of birth; (vi) user name and password associated with your account; (vii) and demographic information (collectively, "Personal Information"), for example, to create an account on the Services or to sign up for our email digest. We will also collect any other information that you choose to provide to us through our Services (e.g. subjects you follow or articles you like). 

#### Information Collected About You from Social Networks and Third Parties

We may also collect information about you from other third parties. For example, we may collect information about you from social networking platforms, such as your user name, name, gender, general location, time zone, birthday, your “likes”, profile picture and friends. 

If you “like” or “follow” us on Facebook, Instagram, Twitter or other social media sites, we may collect some information from you, including your name, email address, and any comments or content you post relevant to us.  We may also collect information if you sign up for a promotion or submit information to us through partners or social media sites. 

We may also collect demographics information from public sources and from third-party data and analytics companies, advertising networks, and others. We use this information to enhance the data we already have.

#### Information We Collect Automatically

We may automatically collect information about your use of our Services, including but not limited to your Internet protocol (“IP”) address; geolocation information; unique device identifiers; and other information about your device(s); the type of web browser you are using and browser language; your operating system; your mobile device carrier information; the websites that led you to our Services; the websites you go after leaving our Services; the pages you view on our Services and the content displayed on those pages; the amount of time spent on particular pages; clickthrough’s to other content on or off our site; error logs; the dates and times you access our Services; and other similar information. As described below, we may use cookies to assist in collecting this information. 

We and our service providers may automatically collect location information, including general information (e.g. IP address, city) from your computer or mobile device. You may be asked to share your specific geo-location information with us.  The Services use this location information to provide customized services, content, promotional offers and other information that may interest you. We may also use location information to improve the functionality of the Services. We and our service providers may also collect information regarding your device’s proximity to “beacons”.  If you do not wish to have this location information collected and used by us, please disable your location features on your device.

Our Services and our service providers may use cookies, Internet server logs, and/or clear gifs to collect data about your use of the Services. 

A cookie is a small string of text that a website can send to your browser which helps the website remember and customize your visit. For example, cookies allow us to tailor the Services, and the content or offers we display to you, in order to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet browsers or other software, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block or disable cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions to learn more about these functions (e.g., [Internet Explorer](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies); [Google Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en); [Mozilla Firefox](http://kb.mozillazine.org/Cookies#Firefox); or [Apple Safari](http://support.apple.com/kb/PH5042)). You can also manage the use of Flash technologies, including cookies and local storage objects with the Flash management tools available at [Adobe’s website](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager02.html). If you reject cookies, functionality of the Services may be limited, and you may not be able to take advantage of many of the site's features.

Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, which are embedded invisibly on web pages or in our emails. We or our service providers may use clear GIFs (also known as web beacons, web bugs or pixel tags), in connection with our Services to track the activities of visitors to our Services, help us manage content, and compile statistics about usage of our Services. We or our service providers may also use clear GIFs in emails to our users, to help us track email response rates, identify when our emails are viewed, and track whether our emails are forwarded; and on our site to track ad impressions or clicks, measure the popularity of the Services and associated advertising, and to access user cookies. 

As we adopt additional technologies, we may also gather additional information through other methods. 

The use of our Services without changing your browser cookie settings will indicate your consent to usage of cookies in accordance with this Policy.  

### Use of Information

Curiosity may use your information as follows:

  * To provide you with the all features and functions of the Services; 

  * To communicate with you regarding our Services; 

  * To complete a transaction or service requested by you; 

  * To provide a smooth, efficient, and personalized experience while using our Services; 

  * To send you information about your relationship or transactions with us, account alerts, or communications, such as newsletters to which you have subscribed;  

  * With your consent, to send push notifications; 

  * To deliver services, such as educational programs, information, or content that is of interest to you; 

  * To alert you to special offers, updated information and other new services from Curiosity, or other third parties, or to forward promotional materials; 

  * To fulfill the terms of a promotion, or administer sweepstakes or contests; 

  * For internal research and reporting; 

  * To help us create and publish content and advertising most relevant to you; 

  * To measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others; 

  * To notify you about a material change to this privacy policy or the Terms of Use, if necessary; 

  * To allow you access to certain functions or features of our Site or Application; 

  * To contact you in response to requests or inquiries we may receive from you; 

  * To enforce the legal terms that govern your use of the Services; 

  * To keep our website safe and secure;  

  * To use IP addressed to identify the location of users, to block disruptive user, to establish the number of visits from different countries and to determine the jurisdiction in which you are assessing the services; and 

  * To administer and troubleshoot the Services.  

We may combine information that we collect from you and about you with information we obtain about you from third parties and use such combined information in accordance with this policy.  

We may also use information on an aggregated and anonymous basis. We may this anonymized and./or aggregated data for any purpose, including without limitation for research and marketing, and may also share such data with any third parties, including advertisers, promotional partners, sponsors, event promoters, and/or others

If you ever provide us with information classified as ‘sensitive personal information’ (e.g. racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs, trade union membership, physical or mental health, sexuality, criminal proceedings and offences), we will only use this information to provide the Services you require in accordance with this Policy and we will ask for your consent to such processing. 

### Information Sharing

Curiosity may share your information with third parties in the following contexts:

#### Consent

We may disclose your information to any third parties based on your consent to do so.

#### Service Providers

We may share your information with third-party service providers who perform services on our behalf and for any other legitimate business purposes. These third parties provide a variety of services, including but not limited to, billing, sales, marketing, advertising, market research, customer support, data storage, and legal services. 

#### Business Transfers

If Curiosity becomes involved in a transaction involving the sale of its assets, such as a merger or acquisition, if Curiosity is transferred to another company, or in the event of a bankruptcy, Curiosity may disclose and/or transfer the information we collect about you and/or Content as part of the transaction. If the surviving entity in that transaction is not Curiosity, the surviving company may use the information we collect about you pursuant to its own privacy policies, which may be different from this Policy.

#### Business Partners

We may share your information with our partners with whom we have a business relationship to provide you with special offers, coupons, discounts, promotions, or to offer products or services to you for purchase. These parties have a separate privacy policy that will govern the use of your information that is not subject to our control. 

#### To Protect Curiosity and Others

Curiosity may share your information if required or permitted to do so by law; for fraud protection and credit risk reduction purposes; to protect and defend the rights or property of Curiosity or the users of the Services; to protect the safety of Curiosity or its employees or a member of the public; to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process; or as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.

#### Legal Compliance

We may share the information we collect about you to comply with applicable legal or regulatory obligations, including as part of a judicial proceeding; in response to a subpoena, warrant, court order, or other legal process; or as part of an investigation or request, whether formal or informal, from law enforcement or a government official.

#### Aggregate or Anonymous Information

We may share anonymous or aggregate information about Curiosity users to third-party companies. For example, we may share anonymous or aggregate information to inform a third party’s decision on whether to participate in the Services as an Advertiser to distribute sponsored content or to place ads on our Services, or on other websites. These companies may use such information about your visits to the Services and other websites to provide advertisements on the Services and other websites.

#### Public Forums

Our Services may offer publicly accessible blogs and community forums.  You should be aware that the information you post publicly is available to anyone who accesses our Services.  If you do not want people to know specific information about you, do not post it publicly.  This information may be read, collected and used by others who access this information and it may be used or disclosed to other individuals or entities without our control.  We are not responsible for the use by others of the information that you disclose in public posting areas.  

### Personalized Content and Advertising

#### Online and Email Analytics

We may use applications, servers and other technology provided by third-party companies, such as [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/), to help us analyze how users use our Services, including by noting the third-party website from which you arrive, and the location which you are accessing the service. These entities may use cookies and information-gathering tools, such as web beacons or Flash LSO, to perform their services. The information collected by the technology will be disclosed to or collected by these service providers, who use this information to evaluate your use of the Services. 

We also use Google Analytics for certain purposes related to advertising. To prevent Google Analytics from using your information for analytics, you may install the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).  

If you receive email from us, we may use certain tools, such as clear GIFs to capture data such as when you open our message or click any links or banners our email contains. This data allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our communications and marketing campaigns. 

#### Tailored Content and Advertising

We may personalize the content and advertising that you see when using the Services through third parties such as network advertisers to serve advertisements on our Services and on third-party websites or other media (e.g. social networking platforms). This enables us and these third parties to target advertisements to you for products and services in which you might be interested. The ads may be based on various factors such as the content on the page you are visiting, information you provide, your searched, demographic data, and other information we collect from you. Third-party ad network providers, advertisers, sponsors and/or traffic measurement services may use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (including clear GIFs), Flash LSOs and other tracking technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content to you. These third-party cookies and other technologies are governed by each third party’s specific privacy policy, not this one. 

Users may opt out of many third-party ad networks. For example, you may go to the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) [Consumer Choice Page](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) for information about opting out of interest-based advertising and their choices regarding having information used by [DAA companies](http://www.aboutads.info/participating/). You may also go to the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) [Consumer Opt-Out Page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) for information about opting out of interest-based advertising and their choices regarding having information used by [NAI members](http://www.networkadvertising.org/participating-networks). Users in the European Union should visit the [opt-out page of the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/%20), or [TRUSTe’s Advertising Choices Page](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) to opt-out of receiving tailored advertising from companies that participate in those programs. You may also use the links available in advertisements that appear in the Services and learn more about our advertising practices through the About Our Ads link available through the Services. To opt out of Google Analytics for display advertising or customize Google display network ads, you can visit the [Google Ads Settings page](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

Please note that to the extent advertising technology is integrated into the Services, you may still receive advertisements even if you opt-out of tailored advertising. You may continue to receive advertisements, for example, based on the particular website that you are viewing (i.e., contextually based ads). Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you opt out on the DAA or NAI websites, your opt out may not be effective. Additional information is available on the DAA’s website at [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) or the NAI’s website at [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

When using a mobile application, you may also receive tailored in-application advertisements. Each operating system provides its own instructions on how to prevent deliver of tailored in-application advertisements. You may review the support materials and/or privacy settings with the respective operating systems to opt-out of tailored advertising. You should contact the applicable platform provider for further details of opting out of in-application advertisements. We also may use third-party service providers to deliver advertisements on mobile applications or for mobile application analytics.  You can opt-out from third-party interest-based advertising on some Android devices and Google apps by visiting Google Settings, Ads and then click on ‘Disable ads based on interests.’  You can also opt out of some interest-based advertising on your mobile device by downloading the Truste Privacy App available at: https://www.truste.com/consumer-resources/privacy-app.

Please note that to the extent advertising technology is integrated into the Services, you may still receive advertisements even if you opt-out. In that case, the advertising will not be tailored to your interests. Also, we do not control any of the above opt-out links or whether any particular company chooses to participate in these opt-out programs.  We are not responsible for any choices you make using these mechanisms or the continued availability or accuracy of these mechanisms.

#### Do Not Track Disclosure

We may track your activities once you leave our Services. There is still no universally accepted standard regarding tracking. You may disable certain tracking as discussed above (e.g. by disabling cookies). For more information about tracking, please click [here](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/).

### Privacy of Children

Our Services are not targeted to children under thirteen (13) years of age, and we do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under 13. If we discover that we have inadvertently collected Personal Information from a child under 13 years of age, we will promptly take all reasonable measures to delete that data from our systems.

### Your Choices

#### Account Information

If you ever wish to access, update or delete your information, please contact us at [info@curiosity.com](mailto:info@curiosity.com) or through the contact information below.  Please note that we may maintain copies of a portion of your information even after you have requested its deletion if the information is required to be retained by law.

#### Curiosity Communications

We may send periodic promotional or informational emails to you, about Curiosity and other third party information and offers. In the event you do not wish to receive such emails from Curiosity, you may opt out of such communications by following the opt-out instructions contained within the body of any email message you receive or emailing us at  [info@curiosity.com](mailto:info@curiosity.com) with the information necessary for us to process a request to opt out of such emails. It may take us up to ten (10) business days to process your opt out request. Even if you have opted out of receiving marketing and promotional emails from us, we may still send you transactional emails, such as emails about your account or the services you have requested from us.

#### Interest-Based Advertising

Please see our Interest-Based Advertising section above for more information about your choices regarding online interest-based advertising.

### Your California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident, you may request a list of certain third parties to which we have disclosed personal information, as defined in California’s “Shine the Light” law ([Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.83](http://www.leginfo.ca.gov/cgi-bin/displaycode?section=civ&group=01001-02000&file=1798.80-1798.84)), about you for their own direct marketing purposes. You may make one request per calendar year. In your request, please attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for your response. You may request this information in writing by contacting us at: [info@curiosity.com](mailto:info@curiosity.com). Please allow up to thirty (30) days for a response.

### International Transfer

If you choose to provide us with your information, Curiosity may transfer that information to its affiliates and subsidiaries or to other third parties, across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. If you are visiting from the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your personally identifiable information to the United States which does not have the same data protection laws as the EU and by providing your personally identifiable information you consent to:

  * The use of your information for the uses identified above in accordance with this privacy policy; and 

  * The transfer of your information to the United States as indicated above. 

### External Links

The Services may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. Curiosity is not responsible for the collection or use of information about you at any third-party sites. Your use of an external website or any informational content found on an external websites is subject to and governed by the terms and guidelines of those website(s). Curiosity does not endorse or make any representations or warranties concerning, and will not in any way be liable for, any informational content, products, services, software, or other materials available on an external website, even if one or more pages of the external website are framed within a page of this Services.

### Security

We have taken steps to protect information we collect about you. Unfortunately, no safeguards or processes can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any such information, and you provide such information at your own risk. If you have an account with us, you should take steps to protect against unauthorized access to your account by, among other things, choosing a robust password that nobody else knows or can easily guess and keeping your log-in and password private. We are not responsible for any lost, stolen, or compromised passwords or for any activity on your account via unauthorized password activity.

### Privacy Policy Modifications

This Policy was last updated as of the “Last Modified” date above. Curiosity may modify this Policy at any time and will post any updates to our Services. We therefore encourage you to review this page frequently for any changes. 

### Contacting Curiosity

If you have any questions or comments about this Policy, please contact us using the information below.

#### Postal Address

    Beacon Solutions, Inc. d/b/a Curiosity.com
    4809 N Ravenswood Ave., Suite 424
    Chicago, IL 60640

#### Email Address
